glo-bus.com 2014-11-21

# Global Business Strategy Simulation Game

##  Your privacy is critically important to us.  
At GLO-BUS Software, Inc. we have a few fundamental principles: 

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. 
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights. 
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services. 

Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals: 

If you have questions about deleting or correcting your personal data please [contact our support team](http://www.glo-bus.com/feedback.html). 

GLO-BUS Software, Inc. operates several websites including bsg-online.com and glo-bus.com. It is GLO-BUS Software, Inc.’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites. 

###  Website Visitors 

Like most website operators, GLO-BUS Software, Inc. collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. GLO-BUS Software, Inc.’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how GLO-BUS Software, Inc.’s visitors use its website. From time to time, GLO-BUS Software, Inc. may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website. 

GLO-BUS Software, Inc. also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users. 

###  Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information 

Certain visitors to GLO-BUS Software, Inc.’s websites choose to interact with GLO-BUS Software, Inc. in ways that require GLO-BUS Software, Inc. to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that GLO-BUS Software, Inc. gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for an account at http://www.glo-bus.com/ to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with GLO-BUS Software, Inc. – by purchasing access to the _GLO-BUS_ service, for example – are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, GLO-BUS Software, Inc. collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with GLO-BUS Software, Inc. GLO-BUS Software, Inc. does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities. 

###  Aggregated Statistics 

GLO-BUS Software, Inc. may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, GLO-BUS Software, Inc. may monitor the IP geolocation of logged-in users to help prevent fraudulent access. GLO-BUS Software, Inc. may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, GLO-BUS Software, Inc. does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. 

###  Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information 

GLO-BUS Software, Inc. discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on GLO-BUS Software, Inc.’s behalf or to provide services available at GLO-BUS Software, Inc.’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using GLO-BUS Software, Inc.’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. GLO-BUS Software, Inc. will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, GLO-BUS Software, Inc. discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when GLO-BUS Software, Inc. believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of GLO-BUS Software, Inc., third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an GLO-BUS Software, Inc. website and have supplied your email address, GLO-BUS Software, Inc. may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with GLO-BUS Software, Inc. and our products. We expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. GLO-BUS Software, Inc. takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information. 

###  Cookies 

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. GLO-BUS Software, Inc. uses cookies to help GLO-BUS Software, Inc. identify and track visitors, their usage of GLO-BUS Software, Inc. website, and their website access preferences. GLO-BUS Software, Inc. visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using GLO-BUS Software, Inc.’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of GLO-BUS Software, Inc.’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies. 

###  Business Transfers 

If GLO-BUS Software, Inc., or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that GLO-BUS Software, Inc. goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of GLO-BUS Software, Inc. may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy. 

###  Privacy Policy Changes 

Although most changes are likely to be minor, GLO-BUS Software, Inc. may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in GLO-BUS Software, Inc.’s sole discretion. GLO-BUS Software, Inc. encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a WordPress.com account, you should also check your blog’s dashboard for alerts to these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
